cryptonoras.com 2018-11-21

# Cryptonoras | Privacy-Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how Cryptonoras, a limited liability company organized and existing under the laws of Norway, with name CRYPTONOR AS and registered address at 125, Myrsætervegen 9, 3522 Bjoneroa, Norway collects, uses, discloses and protects your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains which information we collect, how we use, process and protect your information and what options our users have with regards to their personal information. Personal information is data that can identify or contact a single person. This policy applies to information we collect when you access or use Cryptonoras website, Cryptonoras account, Cryptonoras software and Cryptonoras mobile applications (collectively, "Cryptonoras services") or otherwise interact with us as described below. We are compliant with applicable laws in the countries in which we operate. By using the Cryptonoras services or interacting with us as described below, you confirm that you are aware of this Privacy Policy and that you agree with the collection, use and processing of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy, and in some circumstances, we may provide you with additional notice, including, for example, by adding a statement to the homepage of the Cryptonoras website or by sending you an email notification. We strongly encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access or use Cryptonoras services to stay informed about our information practices and your privacy rights and choices.

#### PROCESSING OF INFORMATION

The Cryptonoras collects and processes the data described herein itself and does not forward or transfer them to any other entity or person. By accessing or using the Cryptonoras services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the collecting and processing of information as described in this Privacy Policy. We retain personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil purposes described in this Privacy Policy, subject to our own legal and regulatory obligations. In accordance with our record keeping obligations, we will retain account and personal information for at least 2 years after an account is closed.

#### DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

We will only use and disclose your personal information internally in order to:

  * Understand and meet your needs and preferences; 
  * Develop new and enhance existing service and product offerings;
  * Manage and develop our business and operations; 
  * Carry out any purposes for which we have received your consent; and Meet legal and regulatory requirements.
  * We may disclose any information we collect about you, whether you are a current or former customer, with law enforcement, data protection authorities, government officials, and other authorities, when:
  * Compelled by court order or other legal procedure;
  * We believe the disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss;
  * Disclosure is necessary to report suspected illegal activity;
  * Disclosure is necessary to investigate violations of this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use.
  * We obtain your consent or at your direction.
  * Other than in connection with a merger, sale of Cryptonoras's assets, financing or acquisition, we will not sell or rent any of your information to third parties for their own marketing purposes.

#### SECURITY

We implement reasonable security practices and procedures to help protect the confidentiality and security of your information, including any non-public personal information. We protect your information using reasonable physical, technical and administrative security measures, including by limiting access to your information to employees with a need to know such information. To make sure your personal information is secure; we communicate our privacy and security guidelines to our employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

#### COOKIES

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. They are typically stored on your computer’s hard drive. We use both session and persistent cookies. Session cookies expire when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your computer or mobile device until you erase them or they otherwise expire. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You are free to decline most of our cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but choosing to remove or disable our cookies may interfere with your use and functionality of the Cryptonoras services. Additionally, we may use certain persistent cookies that are not affected by your browser settings, but will use such cookies solely for identity verification and fraud prevention purposes. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, you should be aware that our site, like most other popular sites, may not work well with cookies disabled. For more information about cookies and how to block, delete or disable them, please refer to your browser instructions, or contact us at contact@cryptonoras.com. We use third party service provider(s), to assist us in better understanding the use of our Site. Our service provider(s) will place cookies on the hard drive of your computer and will receive information that we select that will educate us on such things as how visitors navigate around our site, what product is browsed and general transaction information. Our service provider(s) analyses this information and provides us with aggregate reports. The information and analysis provided by our service provider(s) will be used to assist us in better understanding our visitors' interests in our Site and how to better serve those interests. The information collected by our service provider(s) may be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you while you are using our services. Our service provider(s) is/are contractually restricted from using information they receive from our Site other than to assist us.

#### ACCOUNT INFORMATION

You may access and review or update your online account information at any time by logging into your account. If you want to close your account, please contact us at contact@cryptonoras.com. However, please note that if you close your account, we may retain your information as required by law or for our legitimate business purposes, such as to collect fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, prevent fraud or enforce our user agreements.

#### CONTACT US

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at contact@cryptonoras.com.
